When violence is the only option
The Infiltrators is a science fiction, horror film directed by Gary Whitson.
Empress Zarina rules the country of Feminia using her
Imperial Guard Corp Clones as her army.
All males are slaves except for those who have joined the resistance, made
up mostly of a woman who hates the policies of the Empress.
Amanda (Debbie D) Sharpe and Michelle (Laura Giglio) use plastic surgery to make themselves look like
two of the Imperial Clones so that they can infiltrate the enemy and learn their secrets.
But they must defeat General Kala (Pamela Sutch) and Captain Zara
(Barbara Joyce) in order for their mission to be successful.
Amanda Sharpe, played by Debbie D.
General Kala, played by Pamela Sutch.
Michelle, played by Laura Giglio.
Captain Zara, played by Barbara Joyce.
Lakshya (translation: Aim) is a 2004 Indian epic Hindi-language coming-of-age war drama film directed by Farhan Akhtar,
written by his father Javed Akhtar and produced by Ritesh Sidhwani under the banner of Excel Entertainment.
The film stars Amitabh Bachchan, Hrithik Roshan, and Preity Zinta in lead roles.
Based on a story written by Javed in response to discussions with several 1999 Kargil War veterans and army officers, the film follows Karan Shergill, a lazy
young man and the son of a wealthy businessman from Delhi, who joins the Indian Army and matures into a battlefield hero just as war breaks out.
At the 50th Filmfare Awards, Lakshya received 4 nominations, including Best Director (Farhan) and Best Actor (Roshan),
and won 2 awards – Best Choreography (Prabhu Deva for "Main Aisa Kyun Hoon...") and Best Cinematography.
Though the film was a box office failure, it gained a cult following later.
The film was also instrumental in motivating youths
across India to join the Indian Army.
The tone is dark and thought_provoking.